# VISMAY THAKER UNITY | AR/VR DEVELOPER

#### **CONTACT**

✓ vismaythaker008@gmail.com

**\** +91 9427258180

**♀** Ahmedabad.India

**SUMMARY** 

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/thakervismay/

♠ TheDayDreamer17

Self-taught Unity Developer and a passionate gamer. I have worked on some great games of different genres. AR/VR has always brought some sparkles to my eyes. Vuforia, AR core, Wikitude are my top tools. I have worked with Microsoft Holo lens, Oculus Rift, and Oculus Quest

#### **EMPLOYMENT**

Yudiz Solutions Private Limited - Ahmedabad, India Unity Developer - Dec. 2019 to Current Worked collaboratively with highly skilled Unity Developers.

- Created a few prototypes of Doodle Jump,
   BasketBall 3d, 2d Procedural mesh generation, and
   Sequence Game (Card Game).
- Worked on some complex Client Projects in different genres like Machine Learning, Match 2, and Endless runner along VR Simulations.
- Maintained multiple games simultaneously while communicating with Clients to ensure that the company's goals and requirements were met.
- Contributed to R&D Projects such as Implementing the Marching cubes algorithm, Mesh Deformation, Raymarching, and Job System.
- Proactively indulged in all Team bonding activities and Organized some krunker tournaments.
- Guided the trainees in their training period by taking sessions regarding crucial concepts of Unity and helped them in their first game.

AriseGroup - Remote Work Augmented Reality Developer (Contract) -June 2019 to Dec. 2019

- Created an AR app using Unity and ARCore.
- Added creative feedback on feature enhancement and UI design
- Created custom UI scroll tool. (Check it out here)

**Royal Technosoft** - Ahmedabad, India Part Time Faculty - June 2018 to Dec. 2018

- Taught C, C++, JAVA, and Unity Development.
- Created High-level C, and C++ Tests to improve thinking.
- Started a Group to learn and guide others on developing apps on Microsoft Hololens using Unity Game Engine.

#### **SKILLS**

**KEY SKILLS:** Unity, Shaders, Unit Testing, Blender, Good verbal communication skills,

**Documentation writing** 

PLUGINS: AR Core, Unity IAP, Log Viewer, DoTween, Google Ads, Facebook sdk, Photon, Remote Config, Cinemachine, Vuforia, Wikitude, XR Interaction toolkit LANGUAGES: C, C#, C++, Java Script, Python, PHP, JAVA

#### RECOGNITION

DA-IICTCo-Ordinator for an AR/VR Workshop

- Co-ordinated the workshop for AR/VR development in Hololens using Unity Game Engine.
- Presented and explained my creation of ID Badge used by our whole team created using Vuforia tool.

Digimation PVT LTD · Job Requirement Counselor

- I had represented the company Digimation PVT LTD as a Requirement Counsellor at Marwadi University
- Explained the last year students about various IT field jobs and then guide them for their suitable job

### **CREATIVITY**

Drama · Lead Role in commercial play named "TAX FREE"

Content Creator on Youtube · Youtuber

I am a free time content creator, creating funny videos about the famous topics and producing some funny Valorant gameplay clips

#### **EDUCATION**

Gujarat Technological University · Aug. 2016 to Aug. 2020 B.E. Computer Engineering 2020 CGPA-8.99

Shree Narayana Guru Vidyalaya · June 2014 to June 2016 HSC Percentage - 70.6%

Shree Narayana Guru Vidyalaya · June 2013 to June 2014 SSC Percentage - 77.6%



#### **PROJECTS**

# **Toony Bricks**

Toony Bricks is a family of match-based games where the User matches 2 or more matching tiles to clear the level.

- Created a custom level generator tool that uses a custom algorithm that generates level boundaries using Line renderer.
- Designed 100 attractive and gradually challenging levels.
- Developed Daily Bonus system, Gift Boxes, Collectibles, Boosters, and Powerups.

#### Flash It

This app is used to create a measurement graph for visualizing raw material(metal sheets) usage.

- Created a feature to calculate the angles between multiple sheets and the length of a single sheet.
- Generated screenshots and pdf from the final graph.

# **VR Welding**

VR Weld is a product where users can have an immersive experience with different types of welding scenarios using a VR headset.

- Optimized the puddle getting generated in the current project by using low poly models and Unity's Mesh combine.
- Applied marching cubes algorithm for puddle.
- Created custom color-changing shader using extra uv channels for the puddle.

## **TransfrVR**

TRANSFR VR's core technology is a dialogue system between the trainee and a virtual coach. This unique VR apprenticeship model lets trainees move at their own pace and provides strategic, specific feedback to help them learn from their mistakes and master the skills they need to successfully perform their job.

The whole simulation is developed for each of the 3 steps Automated tutorial, Hands-on Practice, and On your own.

- Created custom extensions and generic conditions to reduce redundant code and dependable code respectively.
- Worked with nested prefabs to manage simultaneous workflow between other team members.
- helped with creative decisions to improve the simulation.

#### ML Robot Arm

This is a simulation project where a human sitting in a wheelchair is getting food and water with the help of a Robot arm using **Unity's MLAgent** 

- Created a Proper testable environment containing human, robotic arm, reward functions, and episode end cases.
- Trained the environment by PPO and SAC algorithm.
- Used the TensorFlow graphs to yield maximum results.